Jeremy Moseley

Product Engineer

Victoria, BC CA

jmoseley in Jeremy Moseley

Jeremy is a focused engineer who is intrigued by the design and architecture of distributed systems. He has experience with distributed systems in Typescript, Go, Scala, and Python, and has spent time in most parts of the stack, doing infrastructure, product work, and front-end, truly a fullstack engineer.

| SKILLS — | | | | | |
|----------------------------|-----------------------|-------|------------|------|-----|
| Frontend | Backend | | DevOps | | |
| react html/css | typescript/javascript | node | datadog | bash | aws |
| typescript/javascript next | python postgres | | cloudflare | | |
| redux graphql | distributed systems | mysql | | | |
| WORK EXPERIENCE (5) | | | | | |

Founding Engineer at Cortex Click August 2024- Current

https:://www.cortexclick.com

Wear all the hats. Build a product, chase PMF, talk to customers.

- Technology: Typescript/Javascript, React, Next, Tailwind, Postgres, AWS, Docker, Vercel, React Native
- AI: Mix of GPT-4o, Claude, and others to build out complex multi-step AI workflows and agents
- Best is yet to come

Senior Software Engineer at ClassDojo April 2022- August 2024

https://www.classdojo.com

Scale and expand the capabilities of the messaging platform, supporting millions of active users and thousands of messages per second.

- Built and deployed V2 of the messaging architecture, to enable more complex messaging use cases and to support the growth of the user base.
- Explored solutions for scaling our monolithic database to support various performance and legal requirements.
- Technology: Typescript/Javascript, MySQL, AWS, React, React Native

Senior Software Engineer at Convoy November 2016- April 2022

https://www.convoy.com

Grown with Convoy as it scales its business and organization, from 12 engineers to >200, working on a variety of teams and problem spaces.

 Lead and architected a new platform that replaces Convoys internal user facing tools, and enables Convoy to scale its business operations through the next 10x growth period.

- Built a tool that allowed non-technical users to manage system configuration that previously required an entire engineer worth of effort.
- Mentoring more junior engineers at various stages of their careers (non-traditional background & first job, lightly experienced & starting to tackle larger scope, and traditional background & somewhat experienced).
- Working on projects with Org wide scope, evangelizing and pushing on solutions to large technical project with a large breadth of stakeholders.
- Maintain and extend systems that allow complex integrations with external customer systems.
- Technology: Typescript/Javascript, PostgreSQL, AWS, React

Import/Export Software Engineer 3 at Inkling Systems Inc. June 2015- November 2016 https://www.inkling.com

The Import/Export squad manages all methods for bring content into and out of the Inkling platform, providing infrastructure for converting content from Word to HTML, HTML to EPUB and PDF, as well as conversion to internal formats for Inkling's internal readers.

- Reduced content export errors by 10%, increasing customer satisfaction and reducing customer support overhead.
- Architected a new microservice using the Play framework and an SQS task processor to provide a scalable worker system to allow easy scaling for demand
- Developed a successful Seattle intern program
- Technology: Scala, Java, Play, AWS, SQS, PostgreSQL, Python, XML

Infrastructure Engineer at Inkling Systems Inc. June 2014- June 2015 https://www.inkling.com

The infrastructure team manages infrastructure tooling and AWS deployment of the Inkling stack. Supports other engineering teams to make the system more reliable and easier to work with.

- Implemented a state-of-the-art distributed log systems that handles 30 million events a day.
- Migrated Inkling's deployment and packaging system to Docker, allowing the system to be deployed and managed by state-of-the-art tools
- Significantly reduced downtime caused by deployments
- Increasing engineering efficiency when developing and deploying new services
- Operated as a member of the emergency on-call rotation
- Technology: Scala, AWS, Python, Bash, PostgreSQL, Docker

EDUCATION (2) -

Bachelor Software Engineering at University of Victoria **2009 - 2014**

Associates Degree Computer Engineering Technology at SAIT Polytechnic **2006 - 2007**